

Anas Alaqrabawi

IT Supporter

Emmasvjeh 18 2tv, AARHUS, Denmark

Very technical IT Support Engineer with a danish residence permit, married to a danish citizen, eligible to work in denmark, has terrific troubleshooting and good interpersonal skills to assist customers with computer issues. Possesses a thorough knowledge of computer hardware and software applications. Has a Bachelor's Degree in Computer Information Systems and 6 years of experience working as an IT Support Technician.

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT Support & Helpdesk Engineer Crown Prince Court of Abu Dhabi

06/2015 - 07/2017

Tasks

- Oversee and update assigned support service requests.
- 1st & 2nd Level IT Support.
- Handle daily technical support activities on desktop support including network and applications.
- Adhere to policies as per corporate manuals and directives.
- Train end users on usage of computer hardware and software.
- Test computers to ensure proper functioning of computer systems.

IT Support Engineer

ADNOC Distirbution (Outsourced)

06/2013 - 06/2015

Tasks

- Identify and isolate technical issues and initiate action as appropriate
- Handling the 2nd line level calls for more than 2000 users inside and outside company (branches).
- Consult with business partners to resolve complex international IT problems and issues.
- Network Troubleshooting and Computer Maintenance.
- Install, Troublshoot and monitor Network Printers

IT Support Engineer

AGC Jordan 09/2011 - 06/2013

Tasks

- 1st & 2nd level IT support.
- Install, Troubleshoot and Monitor Printers Network.
- Active Directory Planning and Troubleshooting (Manage User Accounts, Permissions, Group Policies).
- Monitoring & administrating Kaspersky administration kit.

Software Developer

Ayla IT - Jordan

06/2010 – 09/2011 — Tasks

- Develop ERP modules in a proprietary ERP system (Accounting, Inventory, cheques, manufacturing,etc)
- Onsite and remote technical support, Deliver technical training for customers.

SKILLS

Desktop Support Helpdesk ITIL V3

Manage Engine Windows 7 Windows 10

Troubleshooting SCCM 2012 Altiris

2nd Level IT support 1st Level IT Support

Communication Problem solving Independent

EDUCATION

Bsc Degree In Computer Information Systems (09/2006 – 09/2010)

- University Of Jordan

CERTIFICATES

- Microsoft Windows 7, Enterprise Desktop Support Technician Certificate 70-685.
- ITIL 2014.
- MCSE 2012 70-410.
- SCCM 2012.

LANGUAGES

English Full Professional Proficiency Arabic

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Danish

Elementary Proficiency

PROJECTS DURING MY CAREER

Windows XP to 7 Migration

Windows 7 to 8 Migration

IT infrastructure and systems update for the whole company